Inventory of the Center for Civil Society International records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Subject File, 1948-2008. (Box 11-117)
  - General. Material not limited to a specific foreign country or region
    - Religion
      - George H. Gallup International Institute polling data on religion, 1992 (Folder 36: 8)
      - International Prison Ministry, 1979-1991 (Folder 37: 1-4, Folder 38: 1-2)
      - Keston College, 1985-1992 (Folder 38: 3-4)
      - Princeton Religion Research Center, 1988-1990 (Folder 38: 5)
      - Research Center for Religion and Human Rights in Closed Societies, 1980-1989 (Folder 39: 1-2)
      - Rockford Institute, 1986-1989 (Folder 39: 3-4)
      - St. Andrew's Biblical Theological College, 2000-2001 (Folder 40: 1)
      - St. Michael the Archangel Foundation, undated (Folder 40: 2)
      - Seventh-Day Adventist Church, 1987 (Folder 40: 3)
      - Slavic Gospel Association, 1988-1989 (Folder 40: 4)
      - World Council of Churches, 1980-1992 (Folder 40: 5-6)
      - World Vision, 1993-1996 (Folder 40: 7)
      - Youth with a Mission, 1993-1996 (Folder 40: 8)
    - Telecommunications and electronic data
      - General, 1990-1996 (Folder 40: 9)
      - Gopher Project, 1994 (Folder 40: 10)
      - Information referrals, 1994 (Folder 41: 1)
      - Teacher and Student International Communications, 1992-1994 (Folder 41: 2)
    - World and European federalism
      - Association to Unite the Democracies, 1996 (Folder 41: 3)
      - Confrontations Europe, 2002-2004 (Folder 41: 4)
      - European Community, 1992 (Folder 41: 5)
      - Forum of Federations, 2002-2003 (Folder 41: 6)
      - World Federalist Movement, 2000-2004 (Folder 41: 7-9)
    - Lists and miscellany, 1984-2003 (Folder 42: 1-4)
    - Printed matter, 1984-2000 (Folder 42: 5-6, Folder 43: 1-2)
  - Africa, 2001 (Folder 43: 3)
  - Armenia (Folder 43)
    - General, 1995-1997 (Folder 43: 4)
    - Cambridge (Massachusetts)-Yerevan Sister City Project, 1986-2001 (Folder 43: 5)
  - Asia, Central. Material not limited to a single country in the region (Folder 43)
    - General, 1995-2000 (Folder 43: 6-7)
    - Acta Eurasica/Vestnik Evrazii, 1995-1996 (Folder 44: 1)
    - Center InterBilim, 1994 (Folder 44: 2)
    - Central Asia and the Caucacus Conference, Washington, D.C., 2000 (Folder 44: 3)
    - Central Asian Sustainable Development Information Network, 1997-2004 (Folder 44: 4-8)
    - Civil Society in Central Asia Conference, Seattle, Washington, 1998 (Folder 45: 1)
    - Civil Society in Central Asia Project, 1996-1998 (Folder 45: 2)
    - Eurasia Foundation grant, 1997-1999 (Folder 45: 3)
    - Grants and proposals, 1996-1998 (Folder 45: 4-5)
    - Initiative for Social Action and Renewal in Eurasia, 1996-2003 (Folder 46: 1)
    - International NGO Training and Research Centre, 1996-1997 (Folder 46: 2)
    - Internet Resources for Eurasia, Center for Civil Society International publication, by Richard Upjohn and M. Holt Ruffin, 2001 (Folder 46: 3)
    - Islam, 1985-1988 (Folder 46: 4)
    - Maternal and Child Health Central Asian Regional Seminar, Almaty, Kazakhstan, 1993 (Folder 46: 5)
    - National Bureau of Asian Research, 2003 (Folder 46: 6)
    - Non-governmental organizations and resource persons, 1995-2001 (Folder 46: 7-9)
    - Project for Economic Reform and Development in Central Asia, 1993-1995 (Folder 46: 10)
    - Silknet e-mail network, 1993 (Folder 46: 11)
  - Azerbaijan, 1996-1998 (Folder 47: 1)
  - Baltic States. Material not limited to a single country in the region (Folder 47)
    - General, 1991-2001 (Folder 47: 2)
    - Association for the Advancement of Baltic Studies, 1989-2000 (Folder 47: 4-5)
    - Baltic American Freedom League, 1983-1990 (Folder 47: 6)
    - Finerty, John. Report on trip to Baltic States, 1989 (Folder 47: 7)
    - Joint Baltic American National Committee, 1991-1995 (Folder 47: 8)
    - Molotov-Ribbentrop Pact 50th anniversary, 1989 (Folder 47: 9)
    - Russian Baltic Information Center-Blitz, 1994-1995 (Folder 47: 10)
    - U.S.-Baltic Foundation, 1993-1996 (Folder 47: 11)
  - Belarus (Folder 48)
    - General, 1994-1998 (Folder 48: 1)
    - Assembly of Democratic Non-Governmental Organizations of Belarus, 1998-1999 (Folder 48: 2)
    - Belarusian-American Association, 1997-2008 (Folder 48: 3)
    - Belarusian Charitable Fund for the Children of Chernobyl, 1994-1997 (Folder 48: 4)
    - Belorussian American Youth Organization, 1997 (Folder 48: 5)
    - Mass Media Center, Minsk, 1995 (Folder 48: 6)
    - Non-governmental organizations and resource persons, 1997-1998 (Folder 48: 7-8)
    - School of Tomorrow, 1994 (Folder 48: 9)
  - Cambodia
    - Cambodia at Risk Forum, Seattle, Washington, 1989 (Folder 49: 1)
    - Cambodian Network Council, 1990-1993 (Folder 49: 2)
    - Freedom for Cambodia Task Force, 1985-1989 (Folder 49: 3)
    - Will Cambodia Survive? Conference, Seattle, Washington, 1985 (Folder 49: 4)
  - Central America. Material not limited to a single country within the region (Folder 49)
    - General, 1983-1987 (Folder 49: 5)
    - Amparo: Puget Sound Sanctuary News, 1985-1988 (Folder 49: 6)
    - Central America Media Project, undated (Folder 49: 7)
    - Central America Peace Campaign, 1987-1989 (Folder 49: 8)
    - Central America Pluralism Project, 1986-1990 (Folder 49: 9)
    - Central American labor leaders' visit to Seattle, Washington, 1985 (Folder 49: 10)
    - Directory of National Organizations Dealing with Central America. World Without War Council publication. 1987 and 1989 editions (Folder 49: 11)
    - Directory of National Organizations Dealing with Central America 1990 edition (Folder 50: 1)
    - "It's the Real Thing" visit of four Central Americans to Seattle, Washington, 1985 (Folder 50: 2)
    - Non-governmental organizations, 1981-1989 (Folder 50: 3)
    - Pledge of resistance, 1986 (Folder 50: 4)
    - Prodemca/Friends of the Democratic Center in Central America, 1984-1987 (Folder 50: 5)
    - Quixote Center/Quest for Peace, 1985-1990 (Folder 50: 6)
    - Ruffin, M. Holt. Statement on trip to Central America, 1987 (Folder 50: 7)
    - Sanctuary and Political Asylum Project, 1985 (Folder 50: 8)
    - Seattle Central America Policy Conference, Seattle, Washington, 1985 (Folder 51: 1)
    - United States and the Future of Central America Conference, Seattle, Washington, 1984 (Folder 51: 2)
    - Witness for Peace, 1983-1994 (Folder 51: 3)
  - Croatia, 1994-1998 (Folder 51: 4)
  - Cuba (Folder 51)
    - General, 1987-1988 (Folder 51: 5)
    - Comite pro Derechos Humanos en Cuba, undated (Folder 51: 6)
    - Cuban American National Foundation, 1983-1989 (Folder 51: 7, Folder 52: 1-2)
  - Czech Republic (Folder 52)
    - General, 1997-1998 (Folder 52: 3)
    - Foundation for a Civil Society, 1995-1997 (Folder 52: 4)
  - Czechoslovakia (Folder 52)
    - General, 1983-1990 (Folder 52: 5)
    - Charter 77, 1985-1987 (Folder 52: 6)
    - Charter 77 Foundation, 1990 (Folder 52: 7)
    - Civic Forum, 1990 (Folder 52: 8)
    - Committee for Defense of the Unjustly Persecuted, 1988 (Folder 52: 9)
    - Independent Peace Association, Prague, 1988 (Folder 53: 1)
    - Movement for Civil Liberties, 1988 (Folder 53: 2)
    - Wenceslas Square benefit for Charter 77, Seattle, Washington, 1989 (Folder 53: 3)
  - El Salvador (Folder 53)
    - General, 1982-1989 (Folder 53: 4)
    - Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador, 1980-1990 (Folder 53: 5)
  - Estonia (Folder 53)
    - Estonian American National Council, 1990-1994 (Folder 53: 6)
    - Non-governmental organizations and resource persons, undated (Folder 53: 7)
  - Europe, Eastern. Material not limited to a single country within the region (Folder 53)
    - General, 1988-1998 (Folder 53: 8)
    - Across Frontiers, 1987-1988 (Folder 53: 9)
    - American Bar Association Central and Eastern European Law Initiative, 1990-1995 (Folder 53: 10)
    - Centre for Co-operation with Economies in Transition, 1993-1994 (Folder 54: 1)
    - Choruszucha, Lech. Report on trip to Poland and the Soviet Union, 1990 (Folder 54: 2)
    - Civic Education in Eastern and Central Europe Project, 1997 (Folder 54: 3)
    - Courts of Ultimate Appeal II Conference, Strasbourg, France, 1994 (Folder 54: 4)
    - East-West Christian Organizations: A Directory of Western Christian Organizations Working in East Central Europe and the Newly Independent States Formerly Part of the Soviet Union, edited by M. Holt Ruffin and others, 1993 (Folder 54: 5)
    - Financial Services Volunteer Corps, 1992-2000 (Folder 54: 6)
    - Fund for Arts and Culture in Central and Eastern Europe, 1995-2003 (Folder 54: 7)
    - Fundacja Solidarnosci Polsko-Czesko-Slowackiej, undated (Folder 54: 8)
    - Garton Ash, Timothy. Articles, 1988 (Folder 54: 9)
    - GlasNews, 1993-1994 (Folder 55: 1)
    - Green movements, 1990-1991 (Folder 55: 2)
    - Help & Act!on Newsletter, 1986-1989 (Folder 55: 3-6)
    - Institute for Democracy in Eastern Europe, 1988-1999 (Folder 56: 1-2)
    - Institute for East-West Studies, undated (Folder 56: 3)
    - International Center for Journalists Clearinghouse on the Central and East European Press, 1991-1997 (Folder 56: 4)
    - Journalism, 1990-1999 (Folder 56: 5)
    - Law, 2002 (Folder 56: 6)
    - Making Change Last Conference, Washington, D.C., 1992 (Folder 56: 7)
    - Non-governmental Organization Development in Central and Eastern Europe Workshop, Lublin, Poland, 1993 (Folder 56: 8)
    - Non-governmental organizations and resource persons
      - General, 1979-1994 (Folder 57: 1-2)
      - Health, 1991-1994 (Folder 57: 3)
      - Internet, 1987-1995 (Folder 57: 4-5)
      - Religion, 1989 (Folder 57: 6)
    - On Gogol Boulevard, 1985-1990 (Folder 58: 1)
    - Peace movements, 1984-1990 (Folder 58: 2)
    - Philanthropy and nonprofit sector, 1991-1997 (Folder 58: 3-4)
    - Politics and government, 1984-1993 (Folder 58: 5-6)
    - Project Liberty (Harvard University), 1991 (Folder 58: 7)
    - Pubwatch, 1990-1994 (Folder 58: 8)
    - Raising the Curtain: A Guide to Independent Organizations and Contacts in Eastern Europe. World Without War Council publication. First and second editions, 1989 and 1990 (Folder 59: 1)
    - Regional Environmental Center for Central and Eastern Europe, 1994-1995 (Folder 59: 2)
    - Ruffin, M. Holt. Report on trip to Poland and Czechoslovakia, 1988 (Folder 59: 3)
    - Russian, East European and Central Asian Studies Center (University of Washington), 2001-2005 (Folder 59: 4)
    - Stanford Program on International and Cross-Cultural Education, 1991-1992 (Folder 59: 5)
    - Travel, 1986-1989 (Folder 59: 6)
    - United States Catholic Conference Office to Aid the Catholic Church in Central and Eastern Europe and the USSR, 1992 (Folder 59: 7)
    - United States. Congress. Commission on Security and Cooperation in Europe, 1991-1995 (Folder 59: 8)
    - Voluntary Organizations Initiative in Central and Eastern Europe/Eurasia, 1994-1997 (Folder 59: 9)
    - Volya, 1985-1986 (Folder 59: 10)
  - Former Soviet republics. Material not limited to a single country
    - General, 1992-1999 (Folder 60: 1)
    - BEARR Trust, 1994-2004 (Folder 60: 2-3)
    - CEC International Partners, 1984-2003 (Folder 60: 4)
    - Center for Citizen Initiatives, 1989-1998 (Folder 60: 5)
    - Center for Human Rights Advocacy, 1991-1995 (Folder 60: 6)
    - Channels. Center for Civil Society International series of publications, including Channels: Organizations Offering Educational and Service Opportunities in the Commonwealth of Independent States, Baltic Countries, and the Republic of Georgia (1992); Richard Upjohn, Channels: A Guide to Service Opportunities in the Newly Independent States (1993); and M. Holt Ruffin and Joan McCarter, Channels: A Guide to Third Sector Projects, Organizations and Work Opportunities in the New Independent States (1995) (Folder 61: 1-2)
    - Citizen Democracy Corps Conference on Private Sector Assistance to the Commonwealth of Independent States, Washington, D.C., 1992 (Folder 61: 3)
    - Civilian Research and Development Foundation, 1996 (Folder 61: 4)
    - Democracy and Rule of Law Project (Carnegie Endowment), 2000 (Folder 61: 5)
    - Democratic Federalism and Environmental Crisis in the Republics of the Former Soviet Union Conference, Moscow, Russia, 1991 (Folder 61: 6)
    - Fund for Democracy and Development, 1992-1996 (Folder 61: 7)
    - Harvard University Strengthening Democratic Institutions Project, 1992 (Folder 61: 8)
    - Health, 1992-1993 (Folder 61: 9)
    - How the West Works Project, 1992 (Folder 61: 10)
    - Initiative for Social Action and Renewal in Eurasia, 1985-2003 (Folder 61: 11-12)
    - Institute of International Education, 1993 (Folder 61: 13)
    - Interlegal Research Center, 1990-2000 (Folder 62: 1-2)
    - International Research and Exchanges Board, 1993-1995 (Folder 62: 3)
    - Internet Resources for the NIS. Center for Civil Society International publication by Richard Upjohn, 1997 (Folder 62: 4)
    - Medical Working Group Experts Delegation to the New Independent States, 1992 (Folder 62: 5)
    - NIS-US Women's Consortium, 1995-2000 (Folder 62: 6)
    - NIS Women's Directory, 1994 (Folder 62: 7)
    - Non-governmental organizations and resource persons, 1988-1998 (Folder 62: 8)
    - Nonviolence International, 1995 (Folder 62: 9)
    - Private Voluntary Organizations' Initiative for the New Independent States, 1993-1997 (Folder 63: 1-2)
    - Project Kesher, 1997-1999 (Folder 63: 3)
    - Religious Listservs on the Internet, Center for Civil Society International publication, 1995 (Folder 63: 4)
    - Rural Enterprise Adaptation Program, 1992-2003 (Folder 63: 5)
    - Russia, the Caucasus, Central Asia, and Ukraine meeting, New York, New York, 1997 (Folder 63: 6)
    - Sacred Earth Network, 1992-2004 (Folder 63: 7)
    - Socio-Ecological Union, 1995 (Folder 63: 8)
    - United States. Agency for International Development. NIS Task Force, 1992 (Folder 63: 9)
    - United States. Dept. of Commerce. Special American Business Internship Training Program, 1992-1997 (Folder 63: 10)
    - Volunteer Executive Service Team Initiative, 1992 (Folder 64: 1)
    - What Role for the West? Panel, Yale University Law School, 1999 (Folder 64: 2)
  - Georgia, 1989 (Folder 64: 3)
  - Germany (East), 1983-1989 (Folder 64: 4)
  - Hungary
    - General, 1986-2000 (Folder 64: 5)
    - Guardian of Liberty (Nemzetör), 1984-1990 (Folder 64: 6)
    - Hungary Remembered Forum, Seattle, Washington, 1986 (Folder 64: 7)
    - Revolution of 1956 anniversaries, 1986-1996 (Folder 64: 8)
  - Kazakhstan
    - General, 1992-1999 (Folder 65: 1)
    - Almaty Women's Information Center, 1997 (Folder 65: 2)
    - Interlegal Research Center, 1997 (Folder 65: 3)
    - Kazakh-American International Business Institute, 1993 (Folder 65: 4)
    - Kazakhstan International Bureau for Human Rights and Rule of Law, 1996-1998 (Folder 65: 5)
    - Ob'edinenie Pravovoe Razvitie Kazakhstana, 1997 (Folder 65: 6)
  - Kyrgyzstan
    - General, 1994-1997 (Folder 65: 7)
    - Kyrgyz-American Bureau on Human Rights and Rule of Law, 1995 (Folder 65: 8)
    - Women's Support Center, Bishkek, undated (Folder 65: 9)
  - Latin America
    - General, 1982 (Folder 65: 10)
    - Alliance for Latin America, 1989-1990 (Folder 65: 11)
    - Concilio for the Spanish Speaking, 1987 (Folder 65: 12)
    - Council for Human Rights in Latin America, 1989 (Folder 65: 13)
    - Washington Office on Latin America, 1986-1987 (Folder 66: 1)
  - Latvia
    - General, 1986-1997 (Folder 66: 2)
    - American Latvian Association, 1986-1993 (Folder 66: 3-4)
    - Environmental Protection Club of Latvia, 1990-1994 (Folder 66: 5)
    - Jaundalderis, Benita. Visit to Seattle, Washington, 1986 (Folder 66: 6)
  - Lithuania
    - General, 1990-1991 (Folder 66: 7)
    - Draugas Bookstore, Chicago, 1992 (Folder 66: 8)
    - International Executive Service Corps, 1993-1995 (Folder 66: 9)
    - Lietuvos Persitvarkymo Sajudis, 1989 (Folder 66: 10)
    - Lithuanian American Community, Inc., 1992-1993 (Folder 66: 11)
    - Lithuanian Catholic Religious Aid, 1984-1993 (Folder 66: 12)
    - Lithuanian Green Movement, 1994 (Folder 67: 1)
    - Lithuanian International Organizations Committee, 1991 (Folder 67: 2)
    - Non-governmental organizations and resource persons, 1989 (Folder 67: 3)
    - Soviet treaty, Printed copy, 1920 (Folder 67: 4)
    - Supreme Council of the Republic of Lithuania, 1990 (Folder 67: 5-6)
  - Middle East. Foundation on Democratization and Political Change in the Middle East, 1995 (Folder 67: 7)
  - Moldova, 1990-1995 (Folder 67: 8)
  - Nicaragua
    - Appeal for Peace through Negotiations in Nicaragua, 1985 (Folder 67: 9)
    - Belli, Humberto. Visit to Seattle, Washington, 1986 (Folder 67: 10)
    - Cabezas, Omar. Visit to Seattle, Washington, 1986 (Folder 67: 11)
    - Campbell, Francisco. Visit to Seattle, Washington, 1986 (Folder 67: 12)
    - Council for Inter-American Security, 1986 (Folder 67: 13)
    - Cruz, Arturo J. Visit to Seattle, Washington, 1984 (Folder 68: 1)
    - Freedom House, 1985-1989 (Folder 68: 2)
    - Frente Sandinista de Liberación Nacional, 1984 (Folder 68: 3)
    - Puebla Institute, 1987-1988 (Folder 68: 4)
    - Travels to Nicaragua Symposium, Seattle, Washington, 1987 (Folder 68: 5)
    - World Health Organization, undated (Folder 68: 6)
  - Poland
    - General, 1981-1996 (Folder 68: 7)
    - BORDO, undated (Folder 68: 8)
    - Choroszucha, Lech. American-Polish communications project proposal, 1989 (Folder 68: 9)
    - Czaputowicz, Jacek. Visit to Seattle, Washington, 1989 (Folder 68: 10)
    - Foundation in Support of Local Democracy, 1990-1994 (Folder 69: 1)
    - Green Brigades, 1991-1996 (Folder 69: 2)
    - Informator o Organizacjach Pozarzadowych Dzialajacych na Polu Pomocy Spolecznej, 1995 (Folder 69: 3)
    - International Human Rights Conference, Krakow, Poland, 1988 (Folder 69: 4)
    - Jeszcze Raz o Demokracji w Ameryce, Polish translation of Center for Civil Society International publication Civil Society: USA, 1996 (Folder 69: 5)
    - Silesian Dance Theatre, 1994-1995 (Folder 70: 1)
    - Wolnosc i Pokoj (WiP): Documents of Poland's "Freedom and Peace" Movement, World Without War Council publication of English translations of Wolnosc i Pokoj documents, 1989 (Folder 70: 2-3)
    - World War II commemorations, 1994-1997 (Folder 70: 4)
  - Romania
    - General, 1986-1990 (Folder 70: 5)
    - Day of Action for Romania, 1988 (Folder 70: 6)
    - Romanian Free Psychiatrists' Association, 1991-1994 (Folder 70: 7)
    - World Union of Free Romanians, 1987 (Folder 70: 8)
  - Russia. Material relating primarily to the post-Soviet Russian federation
    - Civic education
      - General, 1995-2000 (Folder 71: 1)
      - Citizen's Foundation, 1997 (Folder 71: 2)
      - Darina Cooperation and Development Programme, 1995 (Folder 71: 3)
      - ECHO, Inc., 1996 (Folder 71: 4)
      - Materialy o svobode, undated (Folder 71: 5)
      - Open Society Institute, Moscow, undated (Folder 71: 6)
      - Polishchuk, Leonid. Report to the World Bank, undated (Folder 71: 7)
      - Russian Center for Citizenship Education, 1994 (Folder 71: 8)
      - Russian Science Foundation, 1993-1994 (Folder 71: 9)
      - School of Self-Determination, Moscow, 1993 (Folder 71: 10)
    - Culture
      - General, 1994 (Folder 71: 11)
      - Center of Russian Language and Culture, 1991-1993 (Folder 71: 12)
      - Fellowship for Experimental Art, 1988-1989 (Folder 71: 13)
      - New Academy of Fine Arts, undated (Folder 71: 14)
      - Russian PEN Center, 1993 (Folder 71: 15)
      - Serendipity Russian tours, 1993-2002 (Folder 71: 16)
      - Traverse sport club, 1994 (Folder 71: 17)
      - Printed matter, 1980-1998 (Folder 72: 1-4, Folder 73: 1-2)
    - Economy
      - Accounting, 1993-1995 (Folder 73: 3)
      - Agriculture, 1999 (Folder 73: 4)
      - American Institute of Business and Economics, Moscow, 1994-1996 (Folder 73: 5)
      - Business education, 1994-1995 (Folder 73: 6)
      - Business for Russia Program, 1999 (Folder 73: 7)
      - English-Russian economic terms, 1995 (Folder 73: 8)
      - Financial Services Volunteer Corps, 1997 (Folder 73: 9)
      - Foundation for Russian American Economic Cooperation, 1998 (Folder 73: 10)
      - Housing, 1991-1994 (Folder 74: 1-2)
      - Morozov Project, 1995-1997 (Folder 74: 3)
      - The Revived Elite of Russia's Business/Vozrozhdennaia elita rossiiskogo biznesa, 1997 (Folder 74: 4)
      - Rostov College of Economics and Finance, 1995 (Folder 74: 5)
      - Securities market, 1996 (Folder 74: 6)
      - Soros Foundations Management Training Program, 1993-1997 (Folder 74: 7-8)
      - Twenty-first Century Public Policy Institute (Japan), 2000 (Folder 74: 9)
      - United States. Agency for International Development, 1998 (Folder 75: 1)
      - Volgodonsk Consumers' Association, 1997 (Folder 75: 2)
      - Printed matter, 1993-1998 (Folder 75: 3-4)
    - Education
      - General, 1993-1998 (Folder 75: 5)
      - Council for Scholarship in Russia, 1992 (Folder 75: 6)
      - Partnership between Educational Institutions and Professional Associations proposal, 1994 (Folder 75: 7)
    - Environment
      - General, 1997-1998 (Folder 75: 8)
      - Amiq Institute, 1997-1998 (Folder 75: 9)
      - Baikal Center for Ecological and Citizen Initiatives, 1995-1996 (Folder 75: 10)
      - Bellona, Murmansk, 1995 (Folder 75: 11)
      - Biointensive for Russia, 1995 (Folder 75: 12)
      - Ecodefense Bulletin, 1994-1995 (Folder 75: 13)
      - Environment Ecoline, undated (Folder 75: 14)
      - United States. Agency for International Development. Environmental Policy and Technology Project, undated (Folder 75: 15)
      - Wildlife Foundation, Khabarovsk, 1994 (Folder 75: 16)
      - Printed matter, 1994-1998 (Folder 76: 1-2)
    - Health
      - General, 1993-1999 (Folder 76: 3)
      - Disabled living, 1993 (Folder 76: 4)
      - NAN, 1995 (Folder 76: 5)
    - Human rights
      - Andrei Sakharov Foundation, 1988-1994 (Folder 76: 6)
      - Glasnost Foundation, 1992-1993 (Folder 76: 7)
      - Human Rights Project Group, 1996 (Folder 76: 8)
      - International Center for Human Values, Moscow, 1990-1993 (Folder 76: 9)
      - Memorial, 1993-1998 (Folder 77: 1)
      - Moscow Helsinki Group, undated (Folder 77: 2)
      - Moscow Research Center for Human Rights, 1992-1996 (Folder 77: 3)
      - Mother's Right Foundation, 1997 (Folder 77: 4)
      - Vozvrashchenie (Return) Historico-Literary Society, 1991-1995 (Folder 77: 5)
      - Printed matter, 1993-1998 (Folder 77: 6-7)
    - Journalism
      - General, 1991-1997 (Folder 77: 8)
      - Agentstvo Sotsialnoi Informatsii, 1996 (Folder 78: 1-2)
      - Agentstvo Sotsialnoi Informatsii, 1997 (Folder 78: 3-5, Folder 79: 1)
      - Agentstvo Sotsialnoi Informatsii, 1998 (Folder 79: 2)
      - Ekspress-Khronika, 1995 (Folder 79: 4-5, Folder 80: 1)
      - National Press Institute, 1997 (Folder 80: 2)
      - New Generations, 1994 (Folder 80: 3)
      - New Media for a New World Conference, Moscow, Russia, 1994 (Folder 80: 4)
      - New Media for a New World Conference, Moscow, Russia, 1995 (Folder 80: 5)
      - New Media for a New World Conference, Vladivostok, Russia, 1996 (Folder 80: 6)
      - New Media for a New World Conference, Ekaterinburg, Russia, 1997 (Folder 80: 7)
      - Panorama Information and Research Center, 1991-1999 (Folder 80: 8)
      - Russian Association of the Independent Regional Press, undated (Folder 80: 9)
      - Russian Information Services, 1992-1994 (Folder 80: 10)
      - Russian Story, Inc., undated (Folder 80: 11)
      - Vladivostok News, 1993-1997 (Folder 80: 12)
    - Law
      - General, 1994-2000 (Folder 80: 13)
      - Interlegal Research Center, 1993-1994 (Folder 81: 1)
      - Law and Liberty Trust, 1991-1992 (Folder 81: 2)
    - Localities